Kelly Cashin

Portfolio: https://kellycashin.com | Linkedin: /kellycashin.com | Linkedin: <a href="https://k

kelly.e.cashin@gmail.com

Summary

UX Designer with 3 years experience creating delightful user experiences at SaaS startups with a background in marketing. Skilled in empathetic listening, design thinking, cross-department collaboration and communication. Certificate in UI/UX design through Georgia Tech.

Work Experience

Matcha, Atlanta — *Project Manager*

August 2019 - February 2020

Served as the primary point of communication for users- identified individual user's needs to create a marketing strategy using Matcha's app.

Researched and documented pain points in the user journey to improve the onboarding process and increase product adoption.

Streamlined customer communications into an automated onboarding drip in Intercom to increase engagement and reduce churn.

Collaborated cross-departmentally with product, engineering and marketing teams to write customer best practices and troubleshooting documents.

Saige Chefs, Atlanta — *Marketing Specialist*

June 2018 - August 2019

Designed weekly email marketing campaigns in Mailchimp.

Collaborated with the product team to photograph menu items and write product descriptions.

Strategically produced content across marketing channels to increase SEO and customer engagement.

Worked with the operations team to ensure brand compliance across product.

EncompassRX, Atlanta— Clinical Data Specialist

June 2016 - June 2018

Audited patient data between EMR systems for accuracy.

Instructed pharmacy staff on data-oriented assignments.

Executed analysis work in Excel for patient compliance and outreach projects.

Used empathy to create and communicate greater understanding around patient non-compliance.

Technical Skills

Research: Interviews, Testing Plans, Usability Research, Survey Creation

Analysis: Data synthesis, Data Visualizations

Design: Wireframes, Graphic Design, Web Layouts, Prototypes

Front End Dev: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Github

Internships

Brown Bag Marketing *Creative Intern*June 2012 - August 2012

Elev8 Hire Solutions *Content Writer*|anuary 2014 - April 2014

Education

Georgia Tech UI/UX Certificate 2020

University of GeorgiaGrady College of Journalism 2013 - 2015